{
 "questions_and_answers": [
    {
      "question": "When did campus recruitments at NMAMIT begin?",
      "answer": "Campus recruitments at NMAMIT began in 1994.\nFor further information, visit: https://nmamit.nitte.edu.in/placement.php"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which was the first company to visit the NMAMIT campus for recruitment?",
      "answer": "Kirloskar Snydergeneral was the first company to visit the NMAMIT campus for recruitment.\nFor further information, visit: https://nmamit.nitte.edu.in/placement.php"
    },
    {
      "question": "How many students did Kirloskar Snydergeneral recruit during their first visit?",
      "answer": "Kirloskar Snydergeneral recruited two students during their first visit.\nFor further information, visit: https://nmamit.nitte.edu.in/placement.php"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which company selected two students in 1995 during campus recruitment?",
      "answer": "Wipro selected two students in 1995 during campus recruitment.\nFor further information, visit: https://nmamit.nitte.edu.in/placement.php"
    },
    {
      "question": "What was the number of students selected for jobs on campus by 2000-01?",
      "answer": "By 2000-01, over 150 students were selected for jobs on campus.\nFor further information, visit: https://nmamit.nitte.edu.in/placement.php"
    },
    {
      "question": "In which year did 100% placement for Civil engineering students occur?",
      "answer": "100% placement for Civil engineering students occurred in the year 2004-05.\nFor further information, visit: https://nmamit.nitte.edu.in/placement.php"
    },
    {
      "question": "Is there any year where 100% placement occurred for Civil engineering students?",
      "answer": "100% placement for Civil engineering students occurred in the year 2004-05.\nFor further information, visit: https://nmamit.nitte.edu.in/placement.php"
    },
    {
      "question": "How many students were selected by companies on campus in 2009-10?",
      "answer": "In 2009-10, 317 students were selected by companies on campus.\nFor further information, visit: https://nmamit.nitte.edu.in/placement.php"
    },
    {
      "question": "How many companies recruited students on campus in 2010-11?",
      "answer": "In 2010-11, 64 companies recruited students on campus.\nFor further information, visit: https://nmamit.nitte.edu.in/placement.php"
    },
    {
      "question": "How many students were selected by companies on campus in 2011-12?",
      "answer": "In 2011-12, 774 students were selected by companies on campus.\nFor further information, visit: https://nmamit.nitte.edu.in/placement.php"
    },
    {
      "question": "How many companies recruited students on campus in 2012-13?",
      "answer": "In 2012-13, 61 companies recruited students on campus.\nFor further information, visit: https://nmamit.nitte.edu.in/placement.php"
    },
    {
      "question": "What was the number of students selected by companies on campus in 2013-14?",
      "answer": "In 2013-14, 440 students were selected by companies on campus.\nFor further information, visit: https://nmamit.nitte.edu.in/placement.php"
    },
    {
      "question": "How many companies recruited students on campus in 2014-15?",
      "answer": "In 2014-15, 67 companies recruited students on campus.\nFor further information, visit: https://nmamit.nitte.edu.in/placement.php"
    },
    {
      "question": "What was the number of students selected by companies on campus in 2015-16?",
      "answer": "In 2015-16, 667 students were selected by companies on campus.\nFor further information, visit: https://nmamit.nitte.edu.in/placement.php"
    },
    {
      "question": "How many companies recruited students on campus in 2016-17?",
      "answer": "In 2016-17, 59 companies recruited students on campus.\nFor further information, visit: https://nmamit.nitte.edu.in/placement.php"
    },
    {
      "question": "What was the number of students selected by companies on campus in 2017-18?",
      "answer": "In 2017-18, 668 students were selected by companies on campus.\nFor further information, visit: https://nmamit.nitte.edu.in/placement.php"
    },
    {
      "question": "How many companies recruited students on campus in 2018-19?",
      "answer": "In 2018-19, 86 companies recruited students on campus.\nFor further information, visit: https://nmamit.nitte.edu.in/placement.php"
    },
    {
      "question": "What was the number of students selected by companies on campus in 2019-20?",
      "answer": "In 2019-20, 696 students were selected by companies on campus.\nFor further information, visit: https://nmamit.nitte.edu.in/placement.php"
    },
    {
      "question": "How many companies recruited students on campus in 2020-21?",
      "answer": "In 2020-21, 120 companies recruited students on campus.\nFor further information, visit: https://nmamit.nitte.edu.in/placement.php"
    },
    {
      "question": "What was the number of selections made by companies in 2020-21?",
      "answer": "In 2020-21, 1073 selections were made by companies.\nFor further information, visit: https://nmamit.nitte.edu.in/placement.php"
    },
    {
      "question": "How many selections have been made by companies for the 2021-22 batch?",
      "answer": "For the 2021-22 batch, 998 selections have been made by companies.\nFor further information, visit: https://nmamit.nitte.edu.in/placement.php"
    },
    {
      "question": "How many internships have been offered by companies for the 2021-22 batch?",
      "answer": "For the 2021-22 batch, 68 internships have been offered by companies.\nFor further information, visit: https://nmamit.nitte.edu.in/placement.php"
    },
    {
      "question": "How many companies are currently involved in the placement process for the 2021-22 batch?",
      "answer": "Currently, 84 companies are involved in the placement process for the 2021-22 batch.\nFor further information, visit: https://nmamit.nitte.edu.in/placement.php"
    },
    {
      "question": "Until which month do placements continue for the 2021-22 batch?",
      "answer": "Placements continue until July 2022 for the 2021-22 batch.\nFor further information, visit: https://nmamit.nitte.edu.in/placement.php"
    },
    {
      "question": "How are students who are not successful in placements assisted after graduation?",
      "answer": "Students not successful in placements are assisted for a year after graduation through 'off campus' initiatives/referrals and pool drives.\nFor further information, visit: https://nmamit.nitte.edu.in/placement.php"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the total number of well-known companies that assist NMAMIT in placements annually?",
      "answer": "NMAMIT has an impressive placement record with over 120 well-known companies assisting in placements annually.\nFor further information, visit: https://nmamit.nitte.edu.in/placement.php"
    },
    {
      "question": "How many companies provide industrial exposure/internships to NMAMIT students?",
      "answer": "Over 150 companies provide industrial exposure/internships to NMAMIT students.\nFor further information, visit: https://nmamit.nitte.edu.in/placement.php"
    },
    {
      "question": "What percentage of NMAMIT students pursue higher studies?",
      "answer": "5-10% of NMAMIT students pursue higher studies.\nFor further information, visit: https://nmamit.nitte.edu.in/placement.php"
    },
    {
      "question": "How do some NMAMIT students utilize their time on campus?",
      "answer": "They used to go to libraries and work on projects during their time on campus.\nFor further information, visit: https://nmamit.nitte.edu.in/placement.php"
    }
 ]
}
